American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  December 13, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  December 14, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  December 15, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  December 16, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  December 17-18, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  December 19-20, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  December 21-22, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  December 23, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  December 24-26, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  December 27-28, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  December 29-31, 1915
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  No specific date.
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  January 1-3, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  January 4-6, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  January 7-9, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  January 10-11, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  January 12-13, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  January 14-15, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  January 17, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  January 18, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  January 19, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  January 20-21, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  January 22-24, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  January 25, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  January 26-27, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  January 28, 29, and 31, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  February 1-2, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  February 3-4, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  February 5-7, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  February 8-9, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  February 10-12, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  February 14-15, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  February 16, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  February 17, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  February 18-20, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  February 21-22, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  February 23-24, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  February 25, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  February 26-27, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  February 28-29, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  March 1-2, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  March 3-5, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  March 6-7, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  March 8-9, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  March 10-11, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  March 12-14, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  March 15-16, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  March 17-18, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  March 19-21, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  March 22-23, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  March 24-26, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  March 27-28, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  March 29-30, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  March 31, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  April 1-2, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  April 3-4, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  April 5-6, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  April 7-8, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  April 9-10, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  April 11-12, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  April 13, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  April 15-17, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  April 19-21, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  April 22-24, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  April 25-26, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  April 27-28, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  April 29-31, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  May 1, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  May 2, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  May 3, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  May 4-5, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  May 7-8, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  May 9-10, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  May 11-12, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  May 13-14, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  May 15-16, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  May 17-18, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  May 19-20, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  May 22, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  May 23-24, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  May 25, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  May 26-27, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  May 28-29, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  May 30-31, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  June 1, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  June 2-3, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  June 4-5, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  June 6-7, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  June 8-9, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  June 10-11, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  June 12-13, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  June 14-18, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  June 19-20, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  June 21-23, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  June 24-27, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  June 28-30, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  July 3, 5-7, 10-12 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  July 14, 17, 19-22, 24-26 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  July 28-29, 31 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  August 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 9-11, 13, 15-20, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  August 19, 21, 22, 24, 25, 26, 28, 30, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  September 5, 8, 9, 11-16, 18-20, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  September 22, 25-30, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  October 1, 2, 5-11, 13, 16, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  October 17-21, 23-26, 28-29, 31, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  November 1-10, 13-14, 16-17 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  November 20-22, 24-25, 27-29 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  December 1, 5-6, 8, 11-14, 16, 18, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  December 19-23, 25, 27, 29-30, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  No specific dates
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  January 1-12, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  January 13-19, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  January 20-31, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  February 1-8, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  February 9-21, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  February 22-28, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  March 1-12, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  March 13-31, 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  April 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  May 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  June 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  July-August 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  September 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  October 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  November 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  December 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  January 2, 4, 7-12, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  January 13-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  January 21-24, 26, 28-30, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  February 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  March 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  April 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  May 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  June 1-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  June 19-30, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  July 1-9, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  July 10-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  July 19-31, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  August 1-9, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  August 10-15, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  August 16-21, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  August 22-27, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  August 28-31, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  September 1-10, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  September 11-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  September 19-30, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  October 1-3, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  October 4-9, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  October 10-15, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  October 16-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  October 19-23, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  October 24-26, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  October 28-29, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  October 30-31, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  November 1-5, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  November 6-9, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  November 10-12, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  November 13-15, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  November 16-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  November 19-21, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  November 22-23, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  November 24-27, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  November 29-31, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  December 1-5, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  Decemebr6-9 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  December 10-12, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  December 13-15, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  December 19-18, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  December 19-20, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  December 21-23, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  December 24-27, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  December 28-30, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  December 31, 1918
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  January 1-3, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  January 4-6, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  January 7-9, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  January 10-12, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  January 13-14, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  January 15-17, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  January 18-19, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  January 20-21, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  January 22-24, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  January 25-27, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  January 28-31, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  February 1-4, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  February 5-6, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  February 7-8, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  February 9-10, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  February 11-12, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  February 13-14, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  February 15-16, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  February 17, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  February 18-19, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  February 20-22, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  February 24-25, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  February 26-28, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  March 1-3, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  March 4-6, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  March 7-9, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  March 10-11, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  March 12-13, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  March 14-16, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  March 17-18, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  March 19-21, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  March 22-24, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  March 25-26, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  March 27-28, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  March 29-30, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  March 31, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  April 1-2, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  April 3-4, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  April 5-7, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  April 8-10, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  April 11-12, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  April 14-16, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  April 17-19, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  April 21-22, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  April 23-24, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  April 25-26, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  April 28-29, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  April 30, 1919
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- May1-2, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 91)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 96)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 97)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 98)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 99)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 100)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 72)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 73)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 76)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 81)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 82)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 83)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 41)